Stark, Edward Collection of ILGWU Papers 6254
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Edward Stark Collection of ILGWU Papers
1942-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Stark, Edward
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
6254
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers.
6254235
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Stark, Edward.
6254235
- ILGWU. Open Letters., 1953-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  English, Yiddish, and Spanish
- ILGWU. Resolutions., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  English
- ILGWU. Retirement Fund. Rules and Regulations., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ILGWU. Union Elections., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  English and Yiddish
- Local 9., 1942-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 10., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 22., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  English and Spanish
- Local 35. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 48., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  English and Italian
- Local 60., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 66., 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Local 89., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 117. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Yiddish
- Stark, Edward. Record of Piece Work., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)